questions = [
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT an alias of Christopher George Wallace?",
        "answer_choices": ["Biggie Smalls", "Frank White", "Big Bunny", "Big Poppa"],
        "correct_answer": "Big Bunny"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Which popular rap artist's real name is Nayvadius Wilburn?",
        "answer_choices": ["Birdman", "6lack", "Young thug", "Future"],
        "correct_answer": "6lack"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Harriet Tubman escaped slavery and made about 13 missions to rescue around 70 slaves. What Underground Railroad code name?",
        "answer_choices": ["Abraham", "Passage 187", "Moses", "Red line"],
        "correct_answer": "Moses"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "What American city is considered the home of hip-hop?",
        "answer_choices": ["Dallas", "Los Angeles", "Washington D.C", "New York"],
        "correct_answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Who is the most famous MU Sprinter?",
        "answer_choices": ["Julian Wright", "Usain Bolt", "Sam Johnson", "Ralph Metcalf"],
        "correct_answer": "Usain Bolt"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Where did MLK give his \"I Have a Dream\" speech?",
        "answer_choices": ["white house", "alcatraz", "Lincoln Memorial", "washington monument"],
        "correct_answer": "Lincoln Memorial"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "During the majority of the 20th century African Americans were prevented from voting by",
        "answer_choices": ["literacy tests", "intimidation of violence and economic retaliation", "legacy stipulations such as the grandfather clause", "All of the Above"],
        "correct_answer": "All of the Above"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "What player hit 73 home runs in a season and earned Major League Baseball's Silver Slugger Award 12 times?",
        "answer_choices": ["Jackie Robinson", "Hank Aaron", "Willie Mays", "Barry Bonds"],
        "correct_answer": "Barry Bonds"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "What is the stage name of Trevor Tahiem Smith?",
        "answer_choices": ["Snoop Dog", "Busta Rhymes", "Biggie Smalls", "Wiz Khalifa"],
        "correct_answer": "Biggie Smalls"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "The illegal and discriminatory practice when a professional denies a service such as insurance, loans, mortgage or health providers to a person of color from another district is know as which of the following?",
        "answer_choices": ["Bluelining", "Redlining", "District equity", "District Law"],
        "correct_answer": "Redlining"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Where did the evolution of Jazz music start?",
        "answer_choices": ["Boston, MA", "Orlando, FL", "Harlem, NY", "Chicago, IL"],
        "correct_answer": "Harlem, NY"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Who invented the three-position traffic signal in 1923 that includes the yellow light?",
        "answer_choices": ["Morgan Freeman", "Benjamin Franklin", "JP Knight", "Garret Morgan"],
        "correct_answer": "Garret Morgan"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Who is the most famous African-American Sprinter ever?",
        "answer_choices": ["Jesse Owens", "Christian Coleman", "Justin Gatlin", "Trayvon Bromell"],
        "correct_answer": "Jesse Owens"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Malcom X is one of our Nation's biggest civil rights leader and Islam devotee. He adopted the X to replace the slave name that was forced upon his family. What was his original last name?",
        "answer_choices": ["Baxter", "Little", "Mohammed", "Short"],
        "correct_answer": "Little"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "At its height, what was the slave population in the U.S.?",
        "answer_choices": ["About 1 Million", "About 500,000", "About 2 Million", "About 4 Million"],
        "correct_answer": "About 4 Million"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "True or False. Less than 4% of Marquette University's student population is black.",
        "answer_choices": ["false", "true"],
        "correct_answer": "false"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Who was the first African American to serve as a U.S. Senator?",
        "answer_choices": ["Hiram Revels", "Carol Mosley Braun", "Edward Brooke", "Blanche K. Bruce"],
        "correct_answer": "Hiram Revels"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Which was the first historically black college (HBCU) in America?",
        "answer_choices": ["Howard University", "Wiley College", "Cheyney University", "Lincoln University"],
        "correct_answer": "Lincoln University"
    },
    {
        "category": "black_culture",
        "question_text": "Harriet Tubman was the most productive conductor on the Underground Railroad. What was her codename?",
        "answer_choices": ["Moses", "Jesus", "Jehovah", "Fred"],
        "correct_answer": "Moses"
    },
]
